Animal cruelty, what they doing, and they shouldn't be doing that because if other ethnic groups was doing that, they'd be charged.
I hear you.
How often have you come out here?
Since 2014.
How do you feel?
Upset.
It never gets easier, knowing just what their fate is going to be.
Penelope was the first chicken I ever rescued from Caporos back in 2014.
Before I even knew that there was a teen, I was actually walking to the grocery store
and I stumbled upon this myself and I did everything that I could just to get one chicken
out.
It was successful.
She had a lot of health issues but then she ended up becoming a house chicken and changed
everything.
She started a sanctuary based on that day.
Back in 2018 we actually found a chicken still alive with his throat slit in a
trash bag during the aftermath and he was rescued. Someone saw the bag moving and
they opened it up and realized that he was in there among all these other dead
chickens that were just about to be picked up by sanitation, like within
minutes. And we rushed him to an emergency vet and he ended up surviving.
He gave him emergency surgery and he lived to be almost eight years old and it's
just a miracle in every way, but a lot of evidence that they don't go to the needy.
They get thrown in the trash, 90% of them.
Are there a lot of just birds dead found here in the crates?
Whatever is left they just, they slaughter them. But yeah, a lot of them by the end of the
week, they suffer because of the elements too. They're not in great conditions of course.
There's dehydration, depending on if it's hot outside. We've had it different times a year,
you know like later in October where they've gotten like frostbit and hypothermia.
So yeah, they definitely don't all make it.
And what about, what about Saturday? What were you telling me about Saturday?
Saturday is one of the biggest nights that happens overnight.
And that's until sunrise. It's very, very intense. It's the biggest, the biggest night.